

PROFILE

Exceptionally seasoned and dedicated Engineering Professor with a strong record in teaching. Adept at explaining highly complex engineering theories and practices in a clear and accessible manner to a variety of professional and non-professional audiences. Committed to offering interested students my full attention and expertise to help further their academic and professional goals.

CONTACT

Phone: 8446644095

Permanent Address:

Singanhalli, Jath, Sangli, MH 416404

Residential Address:

GMVIT Hostel, Tala, Raigad, MH

EMAIL: dadasaheb65@gmail.com

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Microsoft Office
- Csi Bridae
- Csi SAP
- Midas Civil
- Staad Pro
- Etabs
- SketchUp Pro
- AutoCad



Scan to open website Full Info available on my website https://dadasahebhipparkar.wordpress.com/

Declaration: I hereby declare that the above said information are true and correct to the best of my knowledge and belief.

HIPPARKAR D. P.

Assistant Professor

MTech Structural Engineering.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Assistant Professor

Jan 2019-Present **Mumbai University**

G. M. Vedak Institute of Technology, Tala,

- Portfolio handled Admission Cell Committee Member
- Provided individual mentoring and advice to students as required.

• Subject Taught- DDSS, SAC, Survey-I

Assistant Professor D.I.E.T. Satara.

May 2017- June 2018 Shivaji University, Kolhapur

- Portfolio handled Exam Coordinator
- Arranged 2 workshops
- Subject Taught- FM-I, SDD-II, Geology

EDUCATION

MTech - Structural Engineering

2015 - 2017

R.I.T, Islampur,

Shivaji University, Kolhapur

CGPI- 7.44, PG Thesis- Seismic and Wind Analysis of Cable Suspension Bridge: A case study of Tacoma Narrow Bridge.

B.E - Civil Engineering

2011 - 2015

S.B.G.I, Miraj,

Shivaji University, Kolhapur

Percentage- 66.19%, UG Thesis- Analysis of Earthquake Resistant Building Using Etabs Software.

CORE QUALIFICATION

- Extensive breadth of experience in engineering instruction at the college
- Strong ability to deliver course material through a variety of teaching methods
- Superior creative and critical thinking abilities
- High multitasking ability to balance teaching and administrative duties
- Outstanding proficiency in technical and software knowledge

PUBLICATIONS

International Papers: 02

- D. P. Hipparkar, et al; Analysis of Old Tacoma Narrows Bridge According Indian Standards, International Engineering Research Journal, (2017) 191-195.
- D. P. Hipparkar, et al; Experimental investigation of Modified Bitumen Using Waste Plastic and Crumb Rubber, IJRDT, Vol-4, Issue-4, (April-2018) 311-318

PARTICIPATIONS

- International Conference on Innovations & Recent Trends in Engineering at A. G. College of Engineering & Polytechnic, Satara, 25th March 2017.
- Construction techies conference on "Smart India" organized by MIT College of Management, Pune, 8th & 9th Feb 2016.

Location: Sangli

Date: 28/08/2019